mediacurrent.com 2019-03-05

# Privacy | Mediacurrent

Visitor Notice  
We will ask you when we need information that personally identifies you (Personal Information) or allows us to contact you. Generally this information is requested when you are asked to register before participating on the message boards or subscribing to our e-newsletter.

Data Collected  
When you visit our website, we may collect, use and store information such as the type of Internet connection and browser you are using, the number of times you visit our web site, the particular pages you view, the date and time you access our site, the length of your visits to our site, your organizations' domain type, your geographic region or country and the type of data you request when visiting our site. We may use this information to improve our site and your user experience.

When visiting our website, you may choose certain actions such as (i) requesting more information about our services; (ii) signing up to receive a newsletter; (iii) or  obtaining more information about career opportunities with us. When you engage in these activities, you provide us certain Personally Identifiable Information, or information that is specific to you as an individual, like your name, email address, residential address and telephone number. We collect and store this Personally Identifiable Information, any updates to such information that you send us, and any modifications that we make to such information.

Cookies  
Our website may employ cookies that our website may send to your browser for storage on your hard drive. We may use such cookies to make use of our site easier by saving your status and preferences upon visits to our site. Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies, but you may be able to change the settings to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If you choose to modify your settings to reject cookies, then it may affect your use of our website.

Security  
Mediacurrent Interactive Solutions strictly protects the security of your personal information and honors your choices for its intended use. We carefully protect your data from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, alteration, or destruction. We employ and maintain technology and security measures designed to protect your information and the integrity of our site. When you submit information to our web site, that information is subject to a variety of protections, including firewalls. However, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed as 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or receive from us. We will never send an email asking you for passwords, credit card information or any similar private information. If you have any questions about the security of our website, please contact us via privacy@mediacurrent.com.

Third-Party Web sites  
You may have the option to enter third party web sites through our website. Since we cannot be assured that such third party web sites follow our privacy policies, we encourage you to ask questions and review the privacy policies of these third parties.

Enforcement  
If for some reason you believe Mediacurrent has not adhered to these principles, please notify us by e-mail at info at mediacurrent dot com, and we will do our best to determine and correct the problem promptly.  
More About Data and Your Protection  
What We Collect

Personal Data we collect directly from you  
The Personal Data that we collect directly from you may include the following:  
if you express an interest in obtaining additional information about our services, request customer support, use our "Contact Us" or similar features, register to use our website, sign up for an event or webinar, or download certain content, we generally require you to provide us with your contact information, such as your name, job title, company name, address, phone number, email address, or username and password;  
if you attend an event, we may, upon your consent, scan your attendee badge which will provide us with your name, title and company name, address, country, phone number and email address;  
if you use and interact with our website, we automatically collect log files and other information about your device and your usage of our website through cookies, web beacons or similar technologies, such as IP-addresses or other identifiers, which may qualify as Personal Data (view the "What device and usage data we process" section below);

Personal Data we collect from other sources  
We may also collect information about you from other sources, including third parties from whom we have purchased Personal Data, and combine this information with Personal Data provided by you. This helps us to update, expand and analyze our records, identify new customers, and create more tailored content that may be of interest to you. In particular, we collect Personal Data from the following sources:  
Business contact information, including mailing address, job title, email address,  phone number, social handles, LinkedIn URL, and technology makeup from third party data providers for the purposes of delivering relevant content, event promotion, and profiling;

What device and usage data we process  
We use common information-gathering tools, such as log files, cookies, web beacons and similar technologies to automatically collect information, which may contain Personal Data, from your computer or mobile device as you navigate our website or interact with emails we have sent you.

Log Files  
As is true of most website, we gather certain information automatically via log files. This collected information may include your Internet Protocol (IP) address (or proxy server), device and application identification numbers, your location, your browser type, your Internet service provider and/or mobile carrier, the pages and files you viewed, your searches, your operating system and system configuration information, and date/time stamps associated with your usage. This information is used to analyze overall trends, to help us provide and improve our website and to guarantee their security and continued proper functioning.  
Cookies, web beacons and other tracking technologies  
We use cookies and similar technologies such as web beacons, tags and Javascript alone or in conjunction with cookies to compile information about usage of our website and interaction with emails from us.

When you visit our website, our servers or an authorized third party may place a cookie on your browser, which can collect information, including Personal Data, about your online activities over time and across different sites. Cookies allow us to track overall usage, determine areas that you prefer, make your usage easier by recognizing you and providing you with a customized experience.

We use both session-based and persistent cookies. Session cookies exist only during one session and disappear from your computer when you close your browser software or turn off your computer. Persistent cookies remain on your computer or device after you close your browser or turn off your computer. You can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level. To opt-out from tracking by Google Analytics, please use the specific opt-out mechanism as indicated here https://www.aboutcookies.org/

We also use web beacons on our website. For example, we may place web beacons in marketing emails that notify us when you click on a link in the email that directs you to one of our website. Such such tracking technologies are used to operate and improve our website and email communications and track the clicking of links or opening of emails. If you’re not opening emails from us, we stop sending.

Notices on behavioral advertising and opt-out  
As described above, we or third parties may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser when you visit our website for the purposes of serving you targeted advertising (also referred to as “online behavioral advertising” or “interest-based advertising”). To learn more about targeted advertising, advertising networks and your ability to opt out of collection by certain third parties, please visit the opt-out pages of the Network Advertising Initiative, [here](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/?c=1#!/), and the Digital Advertising Alliance, [here](http://optout.aboutads.info/?c=2#!/).

To manage the use of targeting or advertising cookies on this website, consult your individual browser settings for cookies. To learn how to manage privacy and storage settings for Flash cookies [click here](https://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager.html#117118). Various browsers may offer their own management tools for removing HTML5 local storage.

Opt-Out from the collection of device and usage data  
You may opt-out from the collection of device and usage data (see "What device and usage data we process" section above) by managing your cookies at the individual browser level. In addition, if you wish to opt-out of interest-based advertising click [here](http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/), or if located in the European Union click [here](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/)).

While some internet browsers offer a “do not track” or “DNT” option that lets you tell website that you do not want to have your online activities tracked, these features are not yet uniform and there is no common standard that has been adopted by industry groups, technology companies or regulators. Therefore, we do not currently commit to responding to browsers' DNT signals with respect to our website.

Social Media Features  
Our website may use social media features, such as the Facebook “like” button, the “Tweet” button and other sharing widgets (“Social Media Features”). You may be given the option by such Social Media Features to post information about your activities on a website to a profile page of yours that is provided by a third party social media network in order to share with others within your network. Social Media Features are either hosted by the respective social media network or hosted directly on our website. To the extent the Social Media Features are hosted by the respective social media networks, the latter may receive information that you have visited our website from your IP address. If you are logged into your social media account, it is possible that the respective social media network can link your visit of our website with your social media profile.

Your interactions with Social Media Features are governed by the privacy policies of the companies providing the relevant Social Media Features.

Purposes for which we process Personal Data and the legal basis on which we rely  
We collect, process your Personal Data for the purposes and on the legal bases identified in the following:  
Providing our website: We will process your Personal Data to the extent this is necessary for the performance of our contract with you for the use of our website and to fulfill our obligations under the applicable terms of use/service; where we have not entered into a contract with you, we base the processing of your Personal Data on our legitimate interest to operate and administer our website and to provide you with content you access and request (e.g., download of certain content from our website);  
Promoting security of our website: We will process your Personal Data by tracking use of our website, creating aggregated, non-personal data, investigating suspicious activity, as well as violations of and enforcement of our terms and policies, to the extent this is necessary for the purpose of our legitimate interests in promoting the safety and security of the systems and application used for our website, and protecting our rights and the rights of others;  
Handling “contact us” requests: If you fill out a “Contact Us” web form or if you contact us by other means, we will process your Personal Data for the performance of our contract with you and to the extent it is necessary for the purpose of our legitimate interests to fulfill your request and communicate with you;  
Managing event registrations and attendance: We will process your Personal Data to plan and host the event or webinar, including related communication with you, on basis of the performance of our contract with you;

Managing payments: If you have provided financial information, we will process your respective Personal Data to check the financial qualifications and collect payments to the extent this is necessary for completing transaction with you under the contract entered into with you;

Developing and improving our website: We will process your Personal Data to analyze trends, track your usage of our website and interactions with emails to the extent this is necessary for our legitimate interests to develop and improve our website and to provide our users with more relevant and interesting content;    

Displaying personalized advertisements and content: We will process your Personal Data to conduct marketing research, advertise to you, provide personalized information about us on and off our website, and other personalized content based upon your activities and interests to the extent it is necessary for our legitimate interests to advertise our website or, where necessary, to the extent you have provided your prior separate consent (please also view "Your rights relating to your Personal Data" below to learn how you can control how your Personal Data is processed by Mediacurrent for marketing purposes);

Sending marketing communications: We will process your Personal Data to send you marketing information, product recommendations and other non-transactional communications (e.g., marketing newsletters, SMS, or push notifications) about us and our affiliates and partners, including information about our services, promotions or events as necessary for our legitimate interests to conduct direct marketing or to the extent you have provided your prior separate consent (please also view "Your rights relating to your Personal Data" section below to learn how you can control how your Personal Data is processed by Mediacurrent for marketing purposes);

Complying with legal obligations: We will process your Personal Data when cooperating with public and government authorities, courts or regulators in accordance with our legal obligations under applicable laws to the extent this requires the processing or disclosure of Personal Data to protect our rights, and is necessary for our legitimate interests to protect against misuse or abuse of our website, to protect personal property or safety, to pursue remedies available to us and limit our damages, to comply with a judicial proceedings, court order or legal process, and/or to respond to lawful requests.

Where we need to collect and process Personal Data by law, or under a contract we have entered into with you and you fail to provide that required Personal Data when requested, we may not be able to perform the contract.

Sharing Data  
We may share your Personal Data with the following recipients:  
Our contracted service providers which provide services such as IT and system administration and hosting, credit card processing, research and analytics, marketing, customer support and data enrichment;

If you use our website to register for an event or webinar organized by a one of our partners, we may share your Personal Data with the partner to the extent this is  required on the basis of the contract with you to process your registration and ensure your participation in the event; in such case, our partner will process the relevant Personal Data as a separate controller and will provide you with further information on the processing of your Personal Data, where required.  
If you attend an event or webinar organized by us, we may share your information with sponsors of the event if: (1) you consent to such sharing via an event registration form; or (2) you allow your attendee badge to be scanned at a sponsor booth. In that event, your information will be subject to the business partners’ respective privacy statements. If you do not wish for your information to be shared, you may choose not to opt-in via event registration or elect not to have your badge scanned at our events;  
With third–party social networks, advertising networks and website, which usually act as separate controllers, so that we can market and advertise on third party platforms and website;

In individual cases we may also share Personal Data with professional advisers acting as processors or joint controllers including lawyers, bankers, auditors and insurers.  
Any Personal Data or other information you choose to submit in our chat rooms on our website may be read, collected, and/or used by others who visit these forums as it is publicly displayed

Children  
Our website are not directed at children. We do not knowingly collect Personal Data from children under the age of 16. If you are a parent or guardian and believe your child has provided us with Personal Data without your consent, please contact us as described in the “Contacting Us” section below and we will take steps to delete such Personal Data from our systems.

How long do we keep your Personal Data?  
We may retain your Personal Data for a period of time consistent with the original purpose of collection. We determine the appropriate retention period for Personal Data on the basis of the amount, nature, and sensitivity of your Personal Data, the potential risk of harm from unauthorized use or disclosure, and whether we can achieve the purposes of the processing through other means, as well as the applicable legal requirements (such as applicable statutes of limitation).  
After expiry of the retention periods, your Personal Data will be deleted. If there is any information that we are unable, for technical reasons, to delete entirely from our systems, we will put in place appropriate measures to prevent any further use of the data.

Your rights  
You have certain rights regarding your Personal Data, subject to local data protection laws. These may include the following rights:  
to access your Personal Data held by us (right to access);  
to rectify inaccurate Personal Data and ensure it is complete (right to rectification);  
to erase/delete your Personal Data to the extent permitted by other legal obligations (right to erasure; right to be forgotten);  
to restrict our processing of your Personal Data (right to restriction of processing);  
to transfer your Personal Data to another controller to the extent possible (right to data portability);  
to object to any processing of your Personal Data carried out on the basis of our legitimate interests (right to object). Where we process your Personal Data for direct marketing purposes or share it with third parties for their own direct marketing purposes, you can exercise your right to object at any time to such processing without having to provide any specific reason for such objection;  
not to be subject to a decision based solely on automated processing, including profiling, which produces legal effects ("Automated Decision-Making");  Automated Decision-Making currently does not take place on our website;  
to the extent we base the collection, processing and sharing of your Personal Data on your consent, to withdraw your consent at any time, without affecting the lawfulness of the processing based on such consent before its withdrawal.

How to exercise your rights  
To exercise your rights, please contact us at privacy@mediacurrent.com We try to respond to all legitimate requests within one month and will contact you if we need additional information from you in order to honor your request. Occasionally it may take us longer than a month, taking into account the complexity and number of requests we receive.

Your preferences for marketing communications  
If we process your Personal Data for the purpose of sending you marketing communications, you may manage your receipt of marketing and non-transactional communications from us by clicking on the “unsubscribe” link or “email preference center” link located on the bottom of our marketing emails. Additionally, you may [unsubscribe here](http://www2.mediacurrent.com/unsubscribe/u/10072/97d83d79b3b4367c84f245c7f2f530ce861d5cb0c41811540a8d6dd2d6573830/652812218). Please note that opting-out of marketing communications does not opt you out of receiving important business communications related to your current relationship with us, such as information about your contract, event registrations, security information, or other communication we are legally required to send.

Contact Us  
To exercise your rights regarding your Personal Data, or if you have questions regarding this Privacy Statement please email us privacy@mediacurrent.com.  
We are committed to working with you to obtain a fair resolution of any complaint or concern about privacy. If, however, you believe that we have not been able to assist with your complaint or concern, and you are located in the EEA, you have the right to lodge a complaint with the competent supervisory authority.  

Changes to this document  
Changes to this document may be made any time without warning. Mediacurrent may or may not notify you of changes in this policy. You will not be notified about changes related to clarification and/or elaboration of parts of this policy.
